Inventory of the Zhongguo di zheng yan jiu suo interviews
Hoover Institution Archives
Zhongguo di zheng yan jiu suo interviews
1977
77086
Zhongguo di zheng yan jiu suo
15 phonotape cassettes, 1 manuscript box (0.4 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Interviews with twenty-one officials who participated in the Taiwan Land Reform Program, 1949-1953, conducted by the China Research Institute of Land Economics. Includes transcripts.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1977.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Interviews with twenty-one officials who participated in the Taiwan Land Reform Program, 1949-1953, conducted by the China Research Institute of Land Economics. Includes transcripts.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Agriculture--Taiwan.; Land tenure--Taiwan.; Taiwan--History--1945-; Phonotapes.
Collection Contents
- Sound recordings, 1997 (Tape Cabinet)
  - Liu, You-Quing, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007520 (Folder 1)
  - Chui, Yong-Ji, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007521 (Folder 2a)
  - Huang, Tong, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007521 (Folder 2b)
  - Lin, Shi-Dang, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007522 (Folder 3)
  - Lin, Shi-Dang, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007523 (Folder 4a)
  - Bao, Te-Zheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007523 (Folder 4b)
  - Zhang, Yan-Sheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007524 (Folder 5a)
  - Zhao, Qi-Xiang, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007524 (Folder 5b)
  - Li, Chang-Jin, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007525 (Folder 6a)
  - Hong, Rui-Jian, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007525 (Folder 6b)
  - Chen, Shao-Shu, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007527 (Folder 7a)
  - Zhu, Quing-Tao, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007527 (Folder 7b)
  - Feng, Xiao-Peng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007528 (Folder 8)
  - Xung, Ding-Sheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007529 (Folder 9)
  - Wu, Sen-Kun, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007530 (Folder 10)
  - Tong, Zhong-Sheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007531 (Folder 11)
  - Wang, Chang-Xi, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007532 (Folder 12)
  - Xiao, Zheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007535 (Folder 13a)
  - Li, Shen-Hua, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007535 (Folder 13b)
  - Chen, Mian-Xiu, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007536 (Folder 14a)
  - Pan, Lian-Fang, sound recording of interview, 1997; Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007536 (Folder 14b)
  - Tan, Lian-Zhao, sound recording of interview, 1997; There is no transcript of this interview. Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007537 (Folder 15a)
  - Bao, Te-Zheng, sound recording of interview, 1997; There is no transcript of this interview. Use copy reference number: 77086_a_0007537 (Folder 15b)
- Interview Transcripts, circa 1997 (Box 1)
  - Liu, You-Quing, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 1)
  - Chui, Yong-Ji, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 1)
  - Huang, Tong, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 1)
  - Lin, Shi-Dang, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Bao, Te-Zheng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Zhang, Yan-Sheng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Zhao, Qi-Xiang, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 2)
  - Li, Chang-Jin, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 3)
  - Hong, Rui-Jian, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 3)
  - Chen, Shao-Shu, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 3)
  - Zhu, Quing-Tao, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 4)
  - Feng, Xiao-Peng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 4)
  - Xung, Ding-Sheng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 4)
  - Wu, Sen-Kun, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 5)
  - Tong, Zhong-Sheng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 5)
  - Wang, Chang-Xi, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 5)
  - Xiao, Zheng, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 6)
  - Li, Shen-Hua, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 6)
  - Chen, Mian-Xiu, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 6)
  - Pan, Lian-Fang, interview transcript, circa 1997 (Folder 1: 6)